[Music]
well hello my dear friends i hope that
all of you are safe hands on wherever
you are and most importantly healthy so
guys today i am going to do something
new and something unique on this channel
and that is product reviews so guys
recently i have got this dash cam from
izeeker so as you see this is a fresh
package from amazon so i haven't opened
it yet i'll be opening it right now in
front of you so let's get started
so this is the icicle dash cam
let's open it
so the first thing that you see is the
user manual
we'll go through it
and this is the
startup guide
okay
and here is the dash cam
it is
simple
lightweight
looks durable
okay let's see
this is the pin probably to insert the
memory card
this is the usb transfer cable
i'm not sure what this is
okay so this is the cable which will go
to your car
this is the most important thing this is
the suction cup so we'll uh so basically
your entire dash cam is supported on
this one
so we'll see and that's pretty much it
the box is pretty much empty right now
so friends i have gone through the quick
start guide of this particular dash cam
the model is gd 100 from isekar
guys this is a pretty straightforward
simple camera
the memory card goes here it supports
from 32 gb all the way up till 128 gb of
micro sd card
this is the pin which i thought was for
ejecting the memory card but it's not
it's only to reset
the camera if needed
it's pretty simple straight forward
there are a couple of buttons over here
and couple of buttons over here to
adjust the functionality
there is a slot over here on which the
suction cup will come so let me add that
and guys one more important thing about
this suction cup is you should not take
off this plastic cover
right now
you should take it off only when you are
about to install or mount this
particular camera on your car otherwise
the suction power will go away okay it
will not be that effective so there is
this latch over here and there is this
slot over here
we can install the suction cup
like this
yeah
and that is pretty much it
so guys with the suction cup now in
place this camera is ready to be mounted
on your car now let's see the wiring of
it
guys this is the car charger that has
come with this particular kit
as you can see the cable is really long
and it can easily
you know you can easily mount it
anywhere on your windshield as you feel
the connection is pretty straight
forward there is this
slot over here and you can insert this
like this and that is pretty much it and
this will go to your
car adapter and that is pretty much it
that's the whole installation
when i am assembling this i will be
taking off the protective cover
and just applying the suction
that's it
so guys now let's turn this camera on
and let's see before that i'll peel off
this
protective film
and now let's start it
okay
and now
your camera is ready
i'm not sure if the quality of this
video looks decent enough we'll have to
test it in the real life scenario and
before that there is also one protective
film over here which i am not removing
at this moment because i have to install
it in the car first and then i'll be
taking it out so guys that's it for the
day
let me take some time to install this in
my car test it in few scenarios in
daylight night evening in different
conditions
and in few days time i'll be completing
this particular video
[Music]
you can see the riding on the pavement
young kids are growing up in basements
online a whole new generation imma make
mine so you better go take it always
they need a new replacement
decentralized can't contain it we're
changing lives yeah upgrading call it
suicidal
[Music]
make all the demons
a generation fueled by creation we live
lives on a small screen nation we
control the airwaves no negotiation i
refuse to think we need saving something
good will come from creation and when we
think that the world is too anxious
we'll adapt
so guys now i have been using the
izeeker gd 100 dash cam for over a week
now
i have put a 64 gigabyte memory card
into the camera and you have seen that i
have shot in different
weather conditions and different times
of the day and to be honest i am pretty
happy with the clarity and with the
performance of the camera
the camera says that it has got a
inbuilt g sensor which means it can
detect motion and it can automatically
record so in order to test this
particular functionality i banged the
door of my car very hard
uh and it recorded as expected so it's
pretty sensitive uh in in that way
uh
now coming to the memory i said i have
already installed a 64 gigabyte memory
card
and for each two minute of recording it
takes around 300 mb of memory so going
by that calculation we can have close to
440 minutes of continuous recording on a
64 gigabyte card and they also have a
loop recording in process which means
you need not format your card as often
they can automatically overlap the
previous recordings and put the new
recording in place
so
at the time of shooting this video this
particular product is available on
amazon for 59.99 uh there are many
better products available in the market
but to be honest with you guys uh given
the price and given the performance i am
pretty happy with it so definitely it's
a value for money and i would definitely
recommend everyone who is planning to
buy a dash cam consider i seeker the
link of which is given in the
description below and
you can definitely go and check it out
they also have many different products
so gd 100 is like the base model you can
have a front and back both camera also
and then they have different features
available on it
so guys with this i in this particular
video i hope you like the contents of it
and
if you have any other suggestions for us
to make videos on we would be more than
happy to take it and try to make videos
on that so guys i would request you all
to please like the video comment on this
video subscribe to our channel if you
have not already done so and then
stay safe stay healthy and take care